Guide to the Hotel Ezra Cornell records, 1926-2011.
Hotel Ezra Cornell records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hotel Ezra Cornell records, 1926-2011.
28-5-2328
Hotel Ezra Cornell.
13 cubic ft.
Photographs, Printed Materials, Movie Film
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Programs, menus, press releases, broadsides, videocassettes and photographs concerning Hotel Ezra Cornell.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Hotel Ezra Cornell is a student-run annual hotel-for-a-day program at the School of Hotel Administration. The first Hotel Ezra Cornell was staged in Prudence Risley Hall in 1926.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Programs, menus, press releases, broadsides, videocassettes and photographs concerning Hotel Ezra Cornell.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hotel Ezra Cornell.; Cornell University.School of Hotel Administration.
Subjects:
Hotel management schools.; Hotel management--Study and teaching.; Hotels.
Form and Genre Terms:
Broadsides.; Videocassettes.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Cornell Hotel Association publications, #4699.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Programs, Menus, Reports, Press Releases and other Administrative Records
Series II. Photographs and Slides
Series III. Audio and Visual Materials
Series IV. Dinner Plates, Glassware and Memorabilia
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Programs, Menus, Reports, Press Releases and other Administrative Records
  - Menus, programs, clippings, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1st and 2nd annual opening program, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2nd and 4th year press releases, 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 5th annual opening program, student itinerary, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 6th year press releases, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 7th year press releases, annual program, annual report, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual report, 1934-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 10 year anniversary press releases, clippings and correspondence, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 11th year press releases, articles, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 12th year guest book, 1937 (Box 7)
  - 12th year and 13th year press releases and program for opening, 1937, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 14th and 15th year programs, news, share certificate, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual report, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 16th year news, seating lists, press releases, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Our Cornell" Souvenir Edition, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 17th year seating lists, programs, menus, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 18th and 19th annual opening programs, press releases, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 20th and 21st year press releases, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 22nd-24th year press releases, programs, seating lists, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report (23rd year), 1948 (Box 15)
  - Annual Report (24th year), 1949 (Box 15)
  - 25th year Silver Anniversary opening programs, news, seating lists, press releases, menu, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 26th year programs, seating lists, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 27th year programs, guest lists, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual report, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - HEC 27 - Front Office Manager's Report, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - 28th year programs, press releases, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 29th year program, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 29th year- Report of the Managing Director, 1954 (Box 13)
  - 30th year programs, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 30th year programs, napkins, sugar packets, match cases, 1955 (Folder 1)
  - 31st year programs, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 32nd year programs, press releases, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual reports, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
  - 33rd year programs, seating lists, press releases, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 34th year guest lists, Cornell guides, program, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 35th year programs, press releases, guide, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 35th year scrapbook pages with photographs and programs, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5-11)
  - 35th year program, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 36th year matchbook, menus, programs, press releases, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 37th year programs, menus, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 38th year programs, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 39th year programs, correspondence, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Decorations Report - Martha Ames, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 40th year programs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 40th year newspaper, menu, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 41st year program, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 42nd and 43rd year press release, program, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 43rd year newspaper, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 44th year programs, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 44th year scrapbook pages with photographs and clippings, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
  - 45th year program, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for the Restructuring of Hotel Ezra Cornell, May 1970 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 46th year program, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 46th year Seminars/Symposia Program, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 47th year bulletins, Statler Golden Anniversary programs, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 48th year guest lists, programs, John Crandall folder, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 49th year program, press releases, function sheets, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 50th anniversary press releases, programs, guest list, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 50th anniversary - History of Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1975 (Box 9)
  - 51st year programs, menus, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Logo contest designs, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 52nd year press release, program, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 53rd year press releases, programs, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 54th year programs, guide, folders, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 55th year programs, guides, guest lists, press releases, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 56th year programs, menus, booklets, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Program and menus, copy of newsletter "A La Carte", 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - 57th year programs, press releases, invitations, guest lists, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 57th year portfolio, bag, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3, 7)
  - 57th year folder, menus, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 58th year programs, press releases, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 58th year programs, press releases, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 59th year programs, press releases, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 60th year certificate of appreciation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 61st year programs, invitation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 62nd year programs, folders, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 63rd year programs, guest book, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 64th year programs, folder, guest book, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 65th year program, Book of Old manuscript, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Menus, 1990 (Box 11)
  - 66th year invitation, final report, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Invitation and Menu, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 67th year programs, press releases, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Invitation and Menus, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 68th year photo albums, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 68th year invitations, final report, key chain, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 69th year programs, invitation, final report, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 70th year napkins, Mosaic of Time, key chain, scrapbook pages, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 71st year programs, report, guest list, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 72nd year program, invitation, report, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 73rd year scrapbook pages, publicity brochure, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 74th year program, report, scrapbook pages, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - 75th year guest guide, folder, programs, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 76th year press release, program, guest guide, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 79th year guest guides, key card, culinary team, programs, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 80th year guest guide, pocket guide, key card, business card, negatives, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - 81st year press release, guide, programs, negatives, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 82nd year guest guide, newspapers, program, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - 83rd year key cards, programs, guest guides, chopsticks, broadsides, newsletters, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
  - 84th year key cards, programs, guest guides, chopsticks, broadsides, newsletters, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - 84th year posters, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 86th year programs, 2011 (Box 9)
  - The Newnormal, March 17-20, 2016 (Box 9)
  - Unknown date miscellany (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
  - Letterhead (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous foam-core mounted reproductions (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
  - Miscellaneous foam core mounts (Box 7)
  - Handouts, form letters, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Purchasing Guidelines, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - HEC Staff Artist Job Description, no date (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Floor Plans, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Event Floor Plans, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Logo Ideas, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Executive Chef Recipes and Supply Requests, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors File, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - HEC 55 files, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - HEC 56 Files, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - HEC 58 Executive Team Manual, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - HEC 62 Function Sheets, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - HEC 62 Recipe Files, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - HEC 63 Function Proposals and Board of Directors Papers, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - HEC 62 Final Report by Executive Chef D. Degan, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - HEC 60 Form Letters, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - HEC 62 and 63 Final Report and Minutes of Board Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Howard Meek Interview Transcript and Reprint from Southern Hotel Journal, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - "The Indestructible American" from the Southern Hotel Journal, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Press Release concerning Howard Meek's death, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Press Release concerning George Boldt and his connection to Cornell, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Reprints of articles concerning the history of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, no dates (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Alumni News - Dedication of Statler Hall, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Hotel Ezra 57 (1990) Final Project Reports and Minutes (Box 13)
  - Hotel Ezra 57 (1990) Final Project Reports and Minutes (Box 14)
- Series II. Photographs and Slides
  - Photograph at the HEC banquet in the Memorial Room in Willard Straight Hall, 1935 (Folder 1)
  - Photographs of 29th Hotel Ezra Cornell, May 1954 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of 30th Hotel Ezra Cornell, May 1955 (Box 15, Folder 2-5)
  - Photographs from various Hotel Ezra Cornell, various dates (Box 15, Folder 6-11)
  - Contact Sheets from various Hotel Ezra Cornell, various dates (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Photographs and Slides from various Hotel Ezra Cornell, various dates (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Negatives from various Hotel Ezra Cornell, various dates (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Slides from 45th, 48th and 53rd Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Slides from 54th, 56th and 57th Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
  - Photographs, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, 1996, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Photograph album, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
  - Photographs, 2002, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Slides of various Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1959-1990 (Box 16)
- Series III. Audio and Visual Materials
  - HEC Misc. Tape 1, ND; V-1462 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 2, ND; V-1463 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 3, September 15, 1998; V-1464 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 4, ND; V-1465 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 5, ND; V-1466 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 6, ND; V-1467 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 7, April 16, 1986; V-1468 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 8, ND; V-1469 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 9, ND; V-1470 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 10, ND; V-1471 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 11, ND; V-1472 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 12, ND; V-1473 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 13, ND; V-1474 (Box 5)
  - HEC: Kristen Osborn (disc 1), undated; 990 (Box 8)
  - HEC: Marketing Team Files [disc 2], undated; 991 (Box 8)
  - HEC: Kristen Osborne to "Boardies" [disc 11], undated; 1000 (Box 8)
  - HEC: Kristen Osborne [disc 12], undated; 1001 (Box 8)
  - HEC-63, 1988; V-5645 (Box 8)
  - HEC 72-78: Eckerd photos, 1997-2003; 1044-1045 (Box 8)
  - HEC 77-79 Backup [disc 9], 2002-2004; 998 (Box 8)
  - HEC Vol. I [disc 7], 2003; 996 (Box 8)
  - HEC [disc 8], 2003; 997 (Box 8)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 38, 2004-04-03; V-1484 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 14, 2004-04-03; V-1475 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 17, 2004-04-03; V-1476 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 19, 2004-04-02; V-1477 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 21, 2004-04-02; V-1478 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 27, 2004-04-03; V-1479 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 28, 2004-04-03; V-1480 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 29, 2004-04-03; V-1481 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 31, 2004-04-03; V-1482 (Box 5)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 32, 2004-04-02; V-1483 (Box 5)
  - HEC-79: Restaurant Rev. Management, Alex Susskind; Hospitality Investments, Lindsay Cragg (Tapes 15-16), 2004-04-03; V-5646 - V-5647 (Box 8)
  - HEC-79: Brand & Portfolio Management in Hospitality (Tapes 18, 20), 2004-04-02; V-5648 - V-5649 (Box 8)
  - HEC-79: Growth of Spas & Its Impact on the Hospitality Industry (Tapes 22-26), 2004-04-02; V-5650 - V-5654 (Box 8)
  - HEC-79: Is IT Important?, Gabe Piccoli; Lessons From Airline, Zachary Shapiro (Tape 30), 2004-04-03; V-5655 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79 [disc 5], 4/1-4/2004; 994 (Box 8)
  - HEC-79: E-Distribution: A Problem or Solution?, 2004-04-02; V-5656 - V-5660 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Guest Guide [disc 13], 2004; 1002 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Board Pics [disc 14], 2004; 1003 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Guest Guide [disc 35], 2004; 1022 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Backup Files [disc 40], 2004; 1025 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Website Backup Files [disc 41], 2004; 1026 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Print Backup Files [disc 42], 2004; 1027 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Posters Backup Files [disc 43], 2004; 1028 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Guest Guide Files [disc 44], 2004; 1029 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Board Pictures [disc 45], 2004; 1030 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: BC at night - 2 images high res, 2004; 1036 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Invitations, 2004; 1037 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: pictures [], 2004; 1038 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79: Guest Guide, 2004; 1039 (Box 8)
  - HEC: Guest Guide (appears to be blank), 2004; 1040 (Box 8)
  - HEC Misc. Tape 39, April 8, 2005; V-1485 (Box 5)
  - HEC-80: Function Flow (Tapes 1-2), February 12, 2005; V-5661 - V-5662 (Box 8)
  - HEC-80: "What Are We Going to do Next? We're Going to Disneyland!", April 8, 2005; V-5663 (Box 8)
  - HEC-80: "Our Industry at a Glance", April 8, 2005; V-5664 (Box 8)
  - HEC-80: Opening Remarks and Panel Discussion: "Flying High For Years to Come", April 8, 2005; V-5665 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: What Guests Notice? Wine & Chocolate [disc 3], 2005; 992 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: BA, FM, Teams & Board Members for Guest Guide [disc 4], 2005; 993 (Box 8)
  - HEC 79 Invitation [disc 6], 2005; 995 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Guest Guide [disc 10], 2005; 999 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Marketing [disc 23], 2005; 1012 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Porsche [disc 24], 2005; 1013 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Name Tags [disc 26], 2005; 1014 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80 (John Ho) [disc 33], 2005; 1020 (Box 8)
  - HEC80: Invite '06 [disc 38], 2005; 1024 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Marketing Materials, 2005; 1041 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: BA, FM, Teams & Board Members: for Guest Guide, 2005; 1042 (Box 8)
  - HEC 81: Guest Guide [disc 27], 2006; 1015 (Box 8)
  - HEC 81: Education Panels [discs 15-22], 2006; 1004-1011 (Box 8)
  - HEC 81: Guest Guide [disc 28], 2006; 1016 (Box 8)
  - HEC 80: Guest Guide FM, BA, Team pics [], 2005; 1043 (Box 8)
  - HEC 81: Guest Guide [disc 25], 2006; 1046 (Box 8)
  - HEC: 81-83 [disc 37], 2006-2008; 714 (Box 8)
  - HEC 82: Hotelie Tailgate [discs 29-31], 2007; 1017-1019 (Box 8)
  - HEC 81: HEC Indesign Templates: What is HEC? Brochure, Press Kit Inserts, Invitation [disc 36], 2007; 1023 (Box 8)
  - HEC 82 [disc 34], 2007; 1021 (Box 8)
  - HEC [disc 47], 2007; 1032 (Box 8)
  - HEC 83 [disc 46], 2008; 1031 (Box 8)
  - HEC 83: Board [discs 48-49], 2008; 1033-1034 (Box 8)
  - HEC 83: Jason's Photos / Low Resolution Proofs [disc 50], 2008; 1035 (Box 8)
  - HEC 83: Photos [disc 32], 2008; 713 (Box 8)
  - HEC 83: Photos [disc 39], 2008; 715 (Box 8)
  - HEC-84: Vegas Past & Present, 2009; V-5666 (Box 8)
  - HEC-84: Operations Panel, 2009; V-5667 (Box 8)
  - HEC-84: Food and Beverage Panel, 2009; V-5668 (Box 8)
  - HEC 84: Photographs, 2009; 1047 (Box 8)
- Series IV. Dinner Plates, Glassware and Memorabilia
  - Coffee Mug - HEC 44, "Inn of the 7 Seas", 1969 (Box 10)
  - Coffee Mug - HEC 60, "A Diamond Jubilee", 1985 (Box 10)
  - Coffee Mug - HEC - "Best Seller", no date (Box 10)
  - Coffee Mug - HEC 63rd, "Recapture the Past", April 22-24, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Coffee Mug - HEC 70, "A Work of Art", April 7-9, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC Take 52, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 53, "Step into Your Imagination", 1978 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 54, "The Great Escape", 1979 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 55, "Venture Aboard", 1980 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 57, "A Touch of Class", 1982 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 58, "A Vintage Year", 1983 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 59, "Talk of the Town", 1984 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 60, "Diamond Jubilee", 1985 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 61, "Uncorking the Magic", 1986 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 62, "A New Road Taken", 1987 (Box 10)
  - Wine Glass - HEC 63, "Recapture the Past", 1988 (Box 10)
  - Champagne Glass - HEC 67, "The Fire of Dragons", 1992 (Box 10)
  - Champagne Glass - HEC 70, "Mosaic of Time", April 7-9, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Carafe - HEC 70, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Ash Tray - HEC 61, "Uncorking the Magic", 1986 (Box 10)
  - Table Jar - Statler Inn - "The Gateway to the University", no date (Box 10)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 57, "The Russian Dynasty", 1982-04-23 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - "Crossroads of America", no date (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 60, "A Diamond Jubilee", 1985 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 61, "Uncorking the Magic", 1986 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 62, "A New Road Taken", 1987 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 64, "A Night on Broadway", April 14, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 65, "Color Your World", 1990-04-20-22 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 67, "Casablanca", 1992-04-10-12 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 67, "Some Like it Hot", 1992-04-10-12 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 67, "Bal du Moulin Rouge", 1992-04-10-12 (Box 12)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 70, "Mosaic of Time", 1995-04-07-09 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 70, "Mambo Caliente", 1995-04-08 (Box 11)
  - Dinner Plate - HEC 70, "A Taste of Home", 1995 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 58, "A Vintage Year", 1983 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 59, "A Run for the Roses", 1984-04-27 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 59, "Talk of the Town", 1984 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - red and white with checkered trim, no date (Box 11)
  - Small plates, 1985-1988 (Box 12)
  - Small plate - HEC 63, 1998-04-22-24 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 65, 1990-04-20-22 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 66, 1991-04-19-21 (Box 11)
  - Small plate - HEC 67, 1992-04-10-12 (Box 11)
  - T-shirt, "Color Your World", 1990-04-20-22 (Box 12)